irishferries.com 2017-11-15

# 

### Privacy Statement 

At irishferries.com we are committed to protecting your privacy. We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to any other company. The information collected about you is only used to process bookings, provide a more personalised service and keep you up to date with our latest developments and special offers.

From time to time we may contact you with relevant offers based on your details. You will have the choice to opt in or out of receiving such communications by indicating so at booking stage and you will have the opportunity on every e-communication we send you to indicate that you no longer wish to receive our direct marketing material.

If you would prefer not to receive details of these special offers you can send an e-mail at any time to [unsubscribe@irishferries.com](mailto:unsubscribe@irishferries.com) or contract Irish Ferries, Po Box 19, Ferryport, Alexandra Road, Dublin 1, Ireland.

You can review and amend your personal details where the account was created on-line by clicking on your account and entering your e-mail address and password.

You have the right to a copy of information we hold about you and to have it corrected, if it's inaccurate. Applications must be in writing to Irish Ferries, Po Box 19, Ferry port, Alexandra Road, Dublin 1, Ireland or [customersupport@irishferries.com](mailto:customersupport@irishferries.com)

We use tracking software to monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us improve the design and layout of the website. This software does not enable us to capture any personal information.

### Cookies

Cookies are small text files that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your web browser. They enable us to recognise your browser but do not collect any personally identifiable information about you.

This site uses cookies to help us analyse customer behaviour and purchasing patterns which we use to help us improve our services. We also make use of session cookies to remember customer input as they progress through the booking process.

We do not collect any information about you using cookies.

You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser; however you should note that this will prevent you availing of the full functionality of this website.

[Click here](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) for more information about cookies and how to stop cookies being installed on your computer or for more detailed information on how Irish Ferries use cookies see our FAQ.

### Security Policy

Your privacy and security is of critical importance at irishferries.com.

When you book online or access your account with Irishferries.com you do so through a secure server. The use of Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology means that all personal information, such as your credit/debit card and address details, will be encrypted as it travels from your computer to the Irishferries.com Booking System. SSL is an industry-standard method that is used to transmit personal information securely over the Internet. Our use of SSL and digital certificates ensures you are actually sending data to Irish Ferries, rather than a third party, so you can be confident of safely and confidentially completing your reservation.

To maintain the accuracy of your data, as well as preventing unauthorized access and correct use of all data, Irishferries.com uses the appropriate physical, electronic, and governance measures to secure the data we collect online.

Please ensure that you keep your irishferries.com account details confidential and set a password that is difficult for others to guess.
